This Sword Scissor was left behind
by the person who killed my father!
（マイク:流子(りゅうこ)）
この片太刀バサミこそ
父さんを殺した犯人が残したものだ
Now, you'll tell me who
this scissor belongs to,
さあ 教えてもらおうか
このハサミの持ち主を！
鬼龍院皐月(きりゅういんさつき)！
Kiryuuin Satsuki!
You said your name
is Matoi Ryuuko?
（皐月）
纏(まとい)流子といったか… なるほど
I see.
You're Matoi Isshin's daughter?
貴様 纏一身(いっしん)の娘か
You know who my father is?!
（流子）
てめえ 父さんを知ってるのか
You're bleeding too much, Ryuuko.
（鮮血(せんけつ)）血を流し過ぎだ 流子
Isn't that what you want?
てめえが欲しがってたんじゃねえか
At this rate of blood loss,
（鮮血）今のままだと
５分後に流子は気絶することになる
you will lose consciousness
in five minutes.
Don't sound so calm about it!
冷静に言うんじゃねえ
We'll talk about this at length the
next time we meet, Kiryuuin Satsuki!
また ゆっくり
話を聞かせてもらうぜ
鬼龍院皐月！
Don't let her escape! After her! After her!
（猿投山(さなげやま)）逃がすな！ 追え追え！
Don't bother.
（皐月）かまうな
B-But, milady!
うっ しかし…
She'll be back.
ヤツなら また来る
それまで放っておけ
Leave her be until then.
Lady Satsuki...
You're as dazzling as always.
（猿投山）
皐月様 相変わらずまぶしすぎる
Your tea, Miss.
（揃(そろい)）お嬢様 お茶でございます
A girl in a Godrobe, eh?
神衣(かむい)を着た女か… フッ
EPISODE 2
SWOONINGLY
SEXY
This is a world tailored to someone's whims and fancies
dareka ga katteni kimeta readymade na
I'll break free of its shackles
kyou wo nugisutete
RYUUKO
MATOI
And sprint toward my goal
hadashi de hashitte iku
Even if I lose my way
machigattatte
GAMAGOORI IRA
SANAGEYAMA UZU
JAKUZURE NONON
INUMUTA HOUKA
Or trip and fall
korondatte
INUMUTA HOUKA
MANKANSHOKU FAMILY
Those wounds will still create
surimuita itami mo
MANKANSHOKU
MAKO
MIKISUGI
AIKUROU
KINAGASE
TSUMUGU
An original future for me
original na ashita ni naru
KIRYUUIN
SATSUKI
I hold my destiny in my own hands
tsukiageta kono te ni nigirishimeta
And it shines ever so brightly
chikai ga hikari ni natte
So until the day I reach you
itsuka kimi ni todoku sono shunkan made
I don't have the time to sit around crying
naiteru hima nante nai kara
My burning passion pours out from within me
hamidashite shimatta atsui omoi ga
And shines like a star in the night sky
yozora de kagayaki dasu
I think I now understand
umarete kita imi ga
Why I was born
wakatta ki ga shita
I'll make all of my dreams come true
negaigoto wa zenbu kono te de
With my own hands
kanaeru
Oh, wow! It's a nearly naked chick!
（少年Ａ）すげえ
ほとんど裸の姉ちゃんだぜ
（薔薇蔵(ばらぞう)）ハァハァハァハァ…
（流子）は！ おらー！
（薔薇蔵）ダハー！ タッ！
You freakin' pervert!
この変態野郎！
さすらいのギターケース
You think you can make a move on Ryuuko, Kanto Vagabond and Guitar Case Drifter?
関東無宿の流子と知って
手 出してんのか あ？
ハサミ… ハサミがねえ！
My scissor! My scissor's gone!
（マコ）流子ちゃん
（流子）おう！
Ryuuko!
Thanks! Be careful, Mako!
This perv tried to—
マコ 気を付けろ
この変態野郎は…
Dad, what do you think you're doing?
父ちゃん 何してんの？
父ちゃん？ えっ 父ちゃん？
えっ え？
"Dad"?
Dad?!
I'm so sorry!
すみませんでした
Wow, I really felt that one!
くー 効いた効いた
姉ちゃん いいパンチだ
You pack a mean punch, Miss!
そりゃそうだよ
マコを助けてくれた恩人だもん
Of course she does!
I owe her for saving my life!
MANKANSHOKU
BARAZOU
She looked like a total badass,
swinging that scissor around half-naked!
（又郎(またろう)）すんげえ腕なんだよ
半分 裸みたいな格好で
ハサミ振るってさ
Nobody in their right mind
could dress like that, though!
MANKANSHOKU
MATAROU
まともな神経なら
あんな格好はできないね
Bite me! It's a long story, all right?
うるせえ！
こっちにも事情があんだよ
痛(いて)えな 俺がここまで
運んでやったのに
That hurt, damn it!
I was the one who carried you here!
If belting my husband or
Matarou makes you feel better,
（好代(すくよ)）
まあ 父ちゃんや又郎を殴って
気が済むんなら—
then please, belt away!
いくらでも殴ってくださいね
MANKANSHOKU
SUKUYO
BACK-ALLEY DOCTOR
MANKANSHOKU
How did I—
（流子）これは…
Daddy treated you!
父ちゃんが治療したんだよ
これでも闇医者だからね
You'd never guess it,
but he's a back-alley doctor.
MANKANSHOKU
If you compare the number of people he's killed to those he's saved,
殺した数と生かした数なら
殺した数のほうが多いよ
he's killed more!
そりゃまずいだろ
That's not a good thing.
Don't worry about it.
心配すんな 死んだヤツからは
クレームは来ねえよ
The dead ones don't sue you.
Oh, right!
I know it's nothing fancy,
but eat all you like!
大したものはないけど
どんどん食べてちょうだい
Go ahead, Ryuuko! Don't be shy!
流子ちゃん
遠慮しないでいいんだよ
何だか よくわかんないものを
コロッケにしたのと—
It's unidentifiable stuff
made into croquettes
何だか よくわかんないものを
ぶち込んだ みそ汁だから
and unidentifiable
stuff in miso soup!
やだねえ 一応 毒じゃないものしか
入れてませんよ
Oh, you! I'll have you know I use
only non-poisonous ingredients.
Better dig in before I eat it all!
（又郎）
食わないとなくなっちゃうよ
Down, Guts! Your food is out there!
（マコ）こら ガッツ
あんたは向こうにあるでしょ
GUTS
We call him Guts 'cause
he's such a greedy guts!
がっついてるからガッツってんだ
You were suffering from a spot of anemia, little lady, so eat up!
（薔薇蔵）おう 姉ちゃん
貧血だったんだから どんどん食え
Don't just sit there, eat!
（マコ）
ぼやぼやしてないで食べる！
The masses... Fools, all of them.
（皐月）民衆 愚かなる者たち
They're pigs in human clothing,
domesticated by the establishment.
彼らは体制に飼いならされた
服を着た豚だ
They must be governed. By me,
Kiryuuin Satsuki, and Honnouji Academy.
この鬼龍院皐月と
本能字(ほんのうじ)学園により—
統治されなければならない
It is we who shall pave
the way to humanity's future.
我々こそが人類の未来を切り開く
The Ultima Uniforms are
weapons to that end.
極(ごく)制服はそのための武器だ
The uniforms that this country
makes its students wear
この国が学生に着せている制服
これは軍服を基にしている
are based on military uniforms.
The raised collars on boys'
uniforms come from the army.
男子の詰め襟は陸軍の—
Girls' sailor uniforms are
just that—naval uniforms.
女子のセーラー服は
その名のとおり海兵のものだ
This country is a state that chose to make its youth wear military uniforms during their education.
この国は若人に軍服を着せて
教育することを選んだ国家だ
Therefore, we at Honnouji Academy
shall treat our uniforms as combat uniforms.
ならば 我々 本能字学園は
制服を戦闘服とする
They shall be symbols of our control over the pigs in human clothing.
服を着た豚たちを
支配する象徴とする
You of the Sewing Club are the chosen elite
of our Human Conquest and Liberation Project.
諸君ら裁縫部は我が人類支配と
開放計画の精鋭たち
Carry out your work
with the utmost care.
心して励め
Thank you for your kind words.
（伊織(いおり)）
お言葉ありがとうございます
（函館(はこだて)）３年丁(てい)組テニス部部長
函館臣子(おみこ) 参りました
Tennis Club Captain, Hakodate Omiko,
Third Year Class D, reporting as ordered.
How are preparations proceeding
for the Hokkaido interleague match?
（皐月）北海道交流試合の
準備はどうだ？
（函館）はっ 部員一同
研さんに努めております
Milady. All club members are devoting themselves entirely to training.
Those ursine hicks from the north will
learn down to the marrow of their bones
本能字学園と鬼龍院皐月様の力—
the might of Honnouji Academy and Lady Kiryuuin Satsuki.
北の田舎熊どもに骨の髄まで
知らしめてやりましょう
This is armed suppression in the guise of an interleague match.
交流試合という名の武力制圧だ
テニス部が成功すれば
北日本の支配は完成する
If the Tennis Club succeeds, our dominance of northern Japan will be complete.
Don't fail us.
失敗するんじゃないぞ
I understand.
（函館）心得ております
This is a Tennis-Spec Athleticism-
Augmenting Two-Star Ultima Uniform.
（伊織）庭球用運動強化型
二つ星極制服
A gift from Lady Satsuki.
皐月様からの賜り物です
おお ついに私専用の
二つ星極制服が！
At last, a Two-Star
Ultima Uniform of my very own!
Thank you, milady!
ありがとうございます
（皐月）
己の使命を全うしろ
Carry out your mission.
Without fail, milady!
（函館）はっ 必ずや！
The entire Tennis Club shall
pull together, redouble its efforts,
テニス部一同 改めて
身を引き締めて交流試合に備えます
and train even harder
for the interleague match!
Why do you not wear
an Ultima Uniform, Miss?
（揃）なぜ極制服を
お召しにならないのですか お嬢様
This sword is more
than sufficient for me.
（皐月）
私には この剣があれば十分だ
（揃）着るに足る服を得ず
ということでしょうか
Are you saying no uniform
is worthy of you?
フン…
Hey, are you awake?
おい 起きてるか？
お前は一体 何なんだ 鮮血
What the hell are you, Senketsu?
（鮮血）四の五の言うな
Quit your quibbling!
Fine. I'll make you wear me by force!
だったら力ずくでも着られてやる！
Wh-What kind of kinky outfit is this?!
（流子）な… 何だ
この破廉恥な格好は！
This is me.
（鮮血）これが私だ
（流子）
何 落ち着いた声 出してんだ
Don't be so matter-of-fact about it!
Get off me! Come off, damn it!
脱げよ いや 脱がれろ？
Anyway, just get away from me,
あー とにかく 私から離れろ
この変態セーラー服
you perverted sailor uniform!
Where'd that power come from?
何だ このパワーは…
This power is yours and mine.
（鮮血）私と君の力だ
君の血を吸い 私は目覚めた
I drank your blood and awakened.
Whenever you put me on—
whenever I am worn by you—
君が私を着て
私が君に着られたとき—
この力は発現する
that power will be manifested.
（流子）お前 何者だ
（鮮血）わからない
What are you?
I don't know.
You don't know?
（流子）“わからない”って…
You just finished calmly
explaining how you worked!
今まで落ち着いて
説明してたじゃねえか
I am able to explain phenomena that are occurring right now.
（鮮血）
今 起こっている現象は説明できる
だが わからないことが多い
However, there is much
that I do not know.
My memory...
記憶… そう 君たちの言葉で言えば
記憶が欠落している
Yes, in your language, you would say that there are gaps in my memory.
Don't you remember anything?
（流子）
覚えてることはないのか？
I do know that the man
who constructed me
（鮮血）私を作った男は—
had a beard, an eye patch,
and wore a white lab coat.
確か ひげで眼帯で
白衣をまとった—
He was stooped, wore sandals,
held a cane in one hand, and had a mouse.
猫背で げたで 片手につえの
ねずみを連れた…
（流子）
そんなの父さんしかいねえ
That could be only
one man—my father!
Father?
（鮮血）“父さん”？
（流子）ああ 纏一身
私の父親だ 私は流子
Yeah, Matoi Isshin. He's my father.
I'm Ryuuko.
My father made you?
お前を父さんが…
ああ… だが これならヤツらに
勝てるかもしれない
But if I have you,
I might be able to beat them!
You're coming with me
for a while, Senketsu.
ちょっとつきあってもらうぞ 鮮血
"Senketsu"?
（鮮血）“鮮血”？
（流子）
呼び名がないと不便だからな
It'll be a pain if I don't
have anything to call you.
And since my blood awakened you,
your name can be Senketsu—"fresh blood".
私の血を吸って目覚めたんなら
お前の名前は鮮血だ
SENKETSU
"FRESH BLOOD"
Just you wait, Kiryuuin Satsuki!
待ってろよ 鬼龍院皐月！
Ryuuko! Wake up!
（マコ）流子ちゃん 起きてよ
早く 朝ご飯 食べないと！
We have to hurry and eat breakfast!
私 今度 遅刻したら
退学なんだよ！
If I'm late for school again,
I'll be expelled!
There's a pretty dramatic difference between the rich and poor here.
（流子）ずいぶん貧富の差が
はっきりしてるな
ここは皐月様が支配する町だから
Well, this city is ruled
by Lady Satsuki.
ONE-STAR
TWO-STAR
Top-tier students get placed in the exclusive residential areas,
ONE-STAR
TWO-STAR
優等生は
高級住宅街に—
ONE-STAR
TWO-STAR
THREE-STAR
ONE-STAR
TWO-STAR
THREE-STAR
ONE-STAR
TWO-STAR
THREE-STAR
ONE-STAR
TWO-STAR
THREE-STAR
ONE-STAR
TWO-STAR
THREE-STAR
ONE-STAR
TWO-STAR
THREE-STAR
ONE-STAR
TWO-STAR
THREE-STAR
ONE-STAR
TWO-STAR
THREE-STAR
ONE-STAR
TWO-STAR
THREE-STAR
ONE-STAR
TWO-STAR
THREE-STAR
ONE-STAR
TWO-STAR
THREE-STAR
ONE-STAR
TWO-STAR
THREE-STAR
ONE-STAR
TWO-STAR
THREE-STAR
ONE-STAR
TWO-STAR
THREE-STAR
ONE-STAR
TWO-STAR
THREE-STAR
ONE-STAR
TWO-STAR
THREE-STAR
ONE-STAR
TWO-STAR
THREE-STAR
私ら劣等生はスラム街
TWO-STAR
THREE-STAR
while lower-tier students
like us get the slums.
TWO-STAR
THREE-STAR
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
THREE-STAR
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
THREE-STAR
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
THREE-STAR
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
THREE-STAR
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
THREE-STAR
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
THREE-STAR
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
THREE-STAR
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
THREE-STAR
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
THREE-STAR
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
THREE-STAR
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
THREE-STAR
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
THREE-STAR
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
THREE-STAR
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
THREE-STAR
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
Your position at school also
determines where you live?
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
（流子）学校でのポジションで
暮らしも決まるのか？
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
HONNOUJI ACADEMY
（マコ）うん わかりやすいでしょ
Yep! Pretty straightforward, huh?
HONNOUJI ACADEMY
Oh, that reminds me.
あっ あ そうだ
Ryuuko, Mom said that
—if you need a place to—
流子ちゃん 母ちゃんがね…
（マコ）住むとこ…
（流子）あ！
Mom said that—
母ちゃんが… 住むとこないなら…
ウチに… しなよって…
if you don't have a place to stay—
you can stay—
with us—
手続きは… しといたから！
She's already filed the paperwork!
Is this really the time
for living arrangements?!
この状況で言うべきことか？
Hey, what's the big idea?!
てめえら 何のつもりだ！
Ah, you're the transfer student
who was rude to Lady Satsuki, as I recall.
（函館）フン 確か お前は
皐月様に無礼を働いた転校生か
Stay out of this.
邪魔をするな 私は
女子テニス部部長…
I'm Hakodate Omiko,
captain of the Girls' Tennis Club.
GIRLS' TENNIS CLUB
CAPTAIN
HAKODATE
OMIKO
Club member Mankanshoku Mako
has failed to fulfill her club obligations,
満艦飾(まんかんしょく)マコは—
テニス部員としての責を
全うしていない
and as such, is now being purged.
そのための粛清である
What did Mako do wrong?
（流子）マコが一体 何をした
She skipped yesterday's club practice.
（函館）
彼女は昨日 部活をサボった
Our rule is that anyone who fails to come to practice must suffer the 110 Million Cannonball Serve.
無断で部を休んだ者には
億千万本弾丸サーブを行うのが—
我がテニス部の決まり
An outsider has no right to
complain about internal club policies.
部外者に文句を言われる
筋合いはない
Yesterday? Mako was being
held hostage yesterday!
（流子）昨日って… マコは昨日
人質になってたじゃないか
Of course she didn't come
to your stupid practice!
部活なんて無理に決まってんだろ！
（函館）勝手に人質などに
なるからいけない
The issue is that she got herself
taken hostage without permission.
Begin.
やれ！
Cut that out, damn it!
いいかげんにしろ
マコ 先に行け！
Go on ahead, Mako!
You'll be expelled if you're late, right?
（流子）遅刻したら退学なんだろ
（マコ）うん！
Yeah!
Thanks a bunch!
I'll see you later, 'kay?
（マコ）
うん ありがとう 先 行くね！
Yup!
So, you're saying that
you will take us on?
（函館）
お前が相手になるというのか？
I owe her for a meal
and a night's lodging.
一宿一飯の恩義があるんでね
How amusing.
面白い
Don't get too full of yourself just because
you defeated Fukuroda from the Boxing Club.
ボクシング部の袋田(ふくろだ)を
倒したくらいで図に乗るなよ
（流子）フン！
お前らの極制服なんか瞬殺してやる
I'm gonna make quick work of
those Ultima Uniforms of yours!
Let's do it, Senketsu!
いくぞ 鮮血！
Hey! Hey, let's do this, Senketsu!
おい おい やるぞ 鮮血
おい おい！
Hey, what's wrong with you?!
（流子）どうした
おいって マジかよ
フン 服に話しかけるとは
とことん残念なヤツだ
Are you kidding me?!
She's talking to her clothes...
How utterly pathetic.
Wake up, damn it! Hey!
What's your problem?!
おい 起きろって おい！
Die!
死ね！
Screw you! There's a reason—
うるせえ 事情が…
What, a total shutout?
No challenge whatsoever.
（函館）何だ ラブゲームか
手応えのない
（美木杉(みきすぎ)）フウ…
Oh, dear...
ハァ… ああ…
You awake, Ryuuko?
（美木杉）気が付いたかい 流子君
あんた 確か先公の…
Wait, aren't you a teacher?
（美木杉）そうだ
君の担任の美木杉愛九郎(あいくろう)だ
That's right.
I'm your homeroom teacher,
Mikisugi Aikurou.
MIKISUGI
AIKUROU
Talk about your crazy
extracurricular lessons.
まったく とんだ課外授業だよ
Hang on, you didn't
undress me, did you?!
あ！ あんた まさか私を…
That's right. I thought I would
...teach you a few things...
そう いろいろと
教えてあげようと思ってね
straight to your body.
君の体に…
You perverted son of a bitch!
この 変態野郎！
Wait, what?! My body won't move!
あれ 何だ？ 体が動かない
Calm yourself.
（美木杉）落ち着きたまえ
何をした？
What did you do?!
（美木杉）麻酔代わりのツボさ
Anesthetic acupuncture.
You seem a little
hot-blooded at the moment,
少し血の気が多すぎるようだから
血抜きをさせてもらうよ
so I thought I might
draw some of it for you.
（流子）ひっ あっ やめて
注射は苦手なんだ
No, don't! I hate needles!
Allow me to tell you why your
Godrobe didn't activate earlier.
さっき神衣が発動しなかった理由を
教えてあげよう
More! Feed me more!
（鮮血）もっとだ もっとくれ
Feed me more blood!
You're awake, Senketsu?
（流子）気が付いたか 鮮血
（鮮血）もっと血をくれ
Ryuuko?
（鮮血）流子か
バッカ野郎 なんで肝心なときに
起きないんだよ！
Why didn't you wake up when I needed you, you dumbass?!
（美木杉）まあまあ 落ち着いて
Now, now, calm down.
You understand now, right?
これでわかっただろう？
Understand what?
何がわかったんだよ
This Godrobe is
awakened by your blood.
この神衣は君の血で目覚める
神衣 神衣って さっきから何だ？
このセーラー服のことか？
What's this "Godrobe" thing
you keep talking about?
You mean this sailor uniform?
そうだ
That's right.
It's a uniform constructed by your father,
君のお父さん 纏一身が作った
極制服を上回る力を持った服だ
Matoi Isshin, and its power surpasses that of the Ultima Uniforms.
Only someone who can master wearing this can fight against Kiryuuin Satsuki.
鬼龍院皐月と対抗できるのは
それを着こなせる者だけだ
Who the hell are you?
あんた何者だ
You must prove to me that
you are worthy of that answer.
君がそれを応えるに足る
人間かどうか証明してくれ
Come again?
何だと
（美木杉）
まずはテニス部部長の函館臣子だ
The first order of business is the
Tennis Club Captain, Hakodate Omiko.
If you can't master this
Godrobe and defeat her,
神衣を着こなして
彼女に勝てなければ—
you don't stand a chance
against Kiryuuin Satsuki.
とても鬼龍院皐月とは戦えない
（美木杉）おお…
急げ 午後の授業が始まるぞ
Better get a move on.
It's almost time for afternoon classes.
次からは この赤手甲(せきてっこう)を使うんだ
Use this Crimson Glove from now on.
It will make it easier for
you to provide it with blood.
効率よく血を与えることができるぞ
CRIMSON
GLOVE
Fine. I'll pound that tennis
club president into the dirt,
（流子）
わかった あのテニス部の部長を
たたきのめして—
洗いざらい聞かせてもらうよ
and then you're gonna tell me everything I want to know.
Looking good, Hakodate.
（猿投山）いい調子だな 函館
（函館）
はい 皐月様から頂いた—
Thank you. It is all thanks to this Tennis-Spec Ultima Uniform I received from Lady Satsuki.
この庭球特化極制服が
あればこそです
The Tennis Club shall
subjugate Hokkaido without fail.
北海道は必ず 我らテニス部が
制圧してきます
What's that about?
（猿投山）あれは？
We have an unmotivated club
member, so we are purging her.
（函館）
ふぬけな部員がおりましたので
粛清しております
Not so fast, people!
（流子）ちょっと待て お前ら
Ryuuko!
（マコ）流子ちゃん！
The transfer student...
（猿投山）転校生か
（函館）フン
You've come for another beating?
（函館）また やられに来たか？
（流子）ケッ 冗談じゃねえ
As if!
This time, I'm gonna
knock you all on your asses!
今度は貴様らを
たたきのめしてやる！
Let's do it, Senketsu!
いくぞ 鮮血！
（函館）
痛そうなうえに恥ずかしそうだな
マゾの露出狂め
That looks both painful and embarrassing, you masochistic exhibitionist!
Bite me! I'm not an exhibitionist!
（流子）うるせえ 露出狂じゃねえ
（函館）
四の五の抜かすな いくぞ！
Quit splitting hairs.
Let's begin! 110 Million Serve!
億千万本サーブ！
Fault! You're disqualified,
transfer student!
（猿投山）フォールト！
反則負けだ 転校生
What?!
（流子）何！
True, you evaded Hakodate's attack,
（猿投山）
確かに函館の攻撃はかわした
but slicing balls in half
is against the rules!
だが ボールを切るなど
試合ならば反則
In other words, you've won
the fight but lost the match!
ケンカに勝って
勝負に負けたってことだ
Listen up! What you're
standing on is a tennis court!
いいか お前が立っているのは
テニスコート
That means you can't say you've won
unless you win according to the rules of tennis!
だったらテニスのルールで
勝たなきゃ 勝ったとは言えねえ
（流子）えっ そんな…
Hey! Why are you
getting all picky now?
何だよ 今さら
昨日のことはどうなってんだよ
What about yesterday?
That was yesterday!
昨日のことは昨日のことだ
This is crazy!
—When we were boxing, we—
はあ？ むちゃくちゃだぞ
ボクシングのときは！
いいから 反則負けだ！
Doesn't matter! You're disqualified!
（マコ）いいえ 勝ってます
No, she won!
Ryuuko won! She won!
流子ちゃんは 流子ちゃんは
勝って 勝ってます
（函館）ああ…
（猿投山）何？
What?
Ryuuko rescued me!
流子ちゃんは
私を助けてくれたんです
She may have lost the match,
but she won at friendship!
勝負に負けたかもしれませんが
友情で勝ってます
Winning at friendship
means winning at life!
友情で勝つということは
人生で勝つということです
（流子）あのね…
Listen...
あなたがそこまで言うのなら
しかたがない
If you're going to be like that,
you leave her no choice!
Ryuuko will win.
流子ちゃんは勝ちます
Even in tennis, even in tennis,
even in tennis, she'll win!
テニスでも テニスでも
テニスでも勝ちます
So, you're saying that
you want to face me,
ほほう
このテニス部主将 函館臣子と—
Tennis Club Captain
Hakodate Omiko, in a tennis match?
テニスの試合をやるというのか
Here! Do your best, Ryuuko!
はい 頑張ってね 流子ちゃん
All right, all right...
わかった わかった
Let's do this!
やってやろうじゃあねえか！
（猿投山）特殊ルールだ
勝負は１ゲーム サーブ権を決めろ
Special rules!
The match is one game!
Decide who serves first!
I'm watching, Ryuuko!
（マコ）見てるよ 流子ちゃん！
She's a rookie. I'll let her serve.
フン 素人相手だ
サーブは譲ってやる
んじゃあ お言葉に甘えて—
I'll take you up on that, then!
I won't hold back!
Ryuuko!
遠慮はしねえぜ！
（マコ）流子ちゃ〜ん！
甘い！
Too weak!
She's fast!
速い…
Ryuuko, that was awesome!
（マコ）流子ちゃん かっこいい！
Love-fifteen!
（猿投山）ラブ フィフティーン
Not bad.
やるじゃねえか
I'm just getting warmed up.
（函館）まだまだ…
皐月様から頂いた—
You're only just beginning to learn the might of the Tennis-Spec Athleticism-Augmenting
庭球用運動強化型
二つ星極制服の—
威力を知るのはこれからだ
Two-Star Ultima Uniform
I received from Lady Satsuki!
（流子）ケッ 面白(おもしれ)え
Interesting!
That won't work this time!
（流子）今度は そうはいかねえ！
（生徒たちの歓声）
（マコ）うまい！
Nice!
Love-thirty!
（猿投山）ラブ サーティー
I knew you'd try that.
（函館）お前がそうくるのは
読めていたからな
（マコ）うひょ〜
That's why I put a
special spin on my serve.
（函館）特殊な回転をかけておいた
Ryuuko, you naughty girl!
（マコ）
いや〜ん 流子ちゃん 破廉恥
（流子）そんなら こっちも
Then I'll do the same!
Here we go!
いくぜ！
Fault!
（猿投山）フォールト！
（流子）ああ… そんな…
Oh, come on!
Double fault! Love-forty!
（猿投山）ダブルフォールト
ラブ フォーティー
Ryuuko, this is your last shot!
流子ちゃん 後がないよ！
（函館）どうした 転校生
さっさとしないか！
What's the matter, transfer student?
Hurry up and serve!
Ryuuko, use the Sword Scissor!
（鮮血）流子
ハサミを使え
Only the Sword Scissor
can withstand our strength!
私と流子の力に耐えられるのは
片太刀バサミだけだ
SWORD
SCISSOR
（流子）わかった
マコ ハサミだ！
Got it!
Mako! My scissor!
（マコ）ふんぬ… てい！
Catch!
...Right, then...
（流子）よーし
This should do it!
これで いけるぜ！
You can't be serious!
そんなのありか？
Faul—
フォール…
It's all right.
（皐月）かまわん
Play along, Hakodate.
相手をしてやれ 函館
Show us all the power
of your Two-Star.
お前の二つ星の力を見せてみろ
Yes, milady!
As you wish!
Kiryuuin Satsuki, you're looking down on people and barking out orders, same as always.
鬼龍院皐月
相変わらず高(たけ)え所から人を見下して
いいように命令出して…
いけすかねえ
It's creepy.
その神衣の力—
You're going to show me
just how much of that
Godrobe's power you can tap into.
お前がどこまで引き出したか
見せてもらおうか
...You bitch...
（流子）てめえ…
You know that this thing
is called a Godrobe?
こいつが神衣だって
知ってやがるのか！
Not so fast. Your opponent is over there.
（皐月）慌てるな！
お前の相手は彼女だ
I'm gonna use you as a live-fire exercise
to loosen up for the Hokkaido away series!
（函館）北海道遠征の肩慣らしに
実戦訓練とさせてもらおう！
Let's do this, then!
やってやろうじゃねえか
On the court, you can
only count on yourself!
（函館）コートでは
頼れるものは１人きり
Nobody gets it!
（流子）
誰もわかっちゃくれないんだよ
（函館）わあ〜！
"Stripped" of the will to fight!
"STRIPPED"
OF THE
WILL
TO FIGHT!
You did it, Ryuuko!
やった〜 流子ちゃ〜ん！
Oh, dear. It looks like
the match can't go on.
（流子）あ〜らら どうやら
試合続行は不可能のようだな
Don't get too full of yourself, bitch.
貴様 調子に乗るなよ
Wait, Sanageyama.
（皐月）待て 猿投山
勝負に勝ったのは その女だ
The winner of the match is that girl.
Lady Satsuki!
（猿投山）皐月様！
So, are you going to tell me?
（流子）さあ聞かせてもらおうか
お前が片太刀バサミの女か
Are you the woman with
the other Sword Scissor?
あ… 何？
What?!
If you wish to know the answer,
（皐月）
答えが知りたければ 腕で聞け
you'll need to prove yourself!
Ryuuko, if you're going to fight,
you must win within two minutes.
（鮮血）流子 戦うなら２分で勝て
そうでないと また君は気絶するぞ
Otherwise, you're going
to pass out again.
お前が血を吸い過ぎたせいなんだよ
That's because you
drank too much blood!
SECRET
SWORD
Secret Sword Bakuzan.
（皐月）
秘剣 縛斬(ばくざん)
BAKUZAN
この剣は
神衣をも断つ
This blade can cut even a Godrobe.
Its edge is even keener
than that scissor's.
この切れ味
そのハサミよりも鋭いぞ
...The pressure's incredible...
Her fighting spirit is amazing!
（流子）
すごい圧… すごい気合いだ
（皐月）ほう…
Mark my words!
覚えとけ！
次こそは決着をつける
Next time, I'll finish
this once and for all!
（流子）行くぞ マコ！
（マコ）おっ おお！
Let's go, Mako!
'Kay!
Forgive me, milady.
（猿投山）申し訳ありません
転校生を侮っていました
I underestimated the transfer student.
Hakodate is demoted to a No-Star.
（皐月）函館は無星に降格だ
As for Hokkaido, set up an
interleague match with the Sumo Club.
北海道へは相撲部の交流試合を組め
As I expected, a Godrobe
is most formidable.
さすが 神衣
この剣を受けるとは…
To think it could
...turn away my blade...
I shall remember this, Matoi Ryuuko.
覚えておくぞ 纏流子
Before the bell rings
chime ga naru mae ni
I sneak out of school
kugurinuketa
Avoiding the adults' vacant stares
otonatachi no haiiro no me
The pointless conversations
tawai no nai kaiwa
Keep going on and on
togirenu mama
As I walk down the slope
sakamichi wo kudatteku
I have nothing to do
nani wo suru demo naku
And nowhere to go
yuku ate sae mo naku
Right now, all I do
tada atashi ima wa ne
Is ignore any and all warnings
donna chuukoku mo mimi wo surinukeru
Because I still want to be free
mada mada suki ni sasete
I'm sorry, but it's not like me
gomen ne e ni kaita you na
To be an exemplary student
yuutosei wa rashiku nai wa
So I undo two of my shirt buttons
shirt no button wo futatsu hazushite
And take the back alley
rojiura no nukemichi
A path of mysterious sweet temptation
amai yuuwaku wa michi
Some things I've kept hidden from everyone
dare ni mo mada hanashite nai
But tonight, I will reveal my secrets to you
atashi no himitsu wo kon'ya oshiete ageru
NEXT EPISODE PREVIEW
（鮮血）鬼龍院皐月
もう一つの神衣の持ち主
Kiryuuin Satsuki...
KIRYUUIN SATSUKI
ANOTHER
Another owner of a Godrobe.
GODROBE
その圧倒的な力の前に
流子と私は なすすべもない
Ryuuko and I are helpless
before that overwhelming power.
OVERWHELMING
RYUUKO AND I
HELPLESS
勝てるのか 流子
Can we win, Ryuuko?
MATOI RYUUKO
次回 キルラキル
「純潔」
EPISODE 3
PURITY
Next time on KILL la KILL, "Purity".
EPISODE 3
PURITY